<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--As obtained from MAL standard search api-->
<anime>
    <entry>
        <id>269</id>
        <title>Bleach</title>
        <english>Bleach</english>
        <synonyms></synonyms>
        <episodes>366</episodes>
        <score>7.99</score>
        <type>TV</type>
        <status>Finished Airing</status>
        <start_date>2004-10-05</start_date>
        <end_date>2012-03-27</end_date>
        <synopsis>15-year-old Kurosaki Ichigo is not your everyday high school student. He has from
            as far he can remember always had the ability to see ghosts and spirits. A fateful day
            arrives as Ichigo encounters the shinigami Kuchiki Rukia, who saves him and his family
            from a Hollow at the cost of injuring herself. During this encounter, with Rukia unable
            to defeat the hollow she transfers her shinigami powers into Ichigo. In the aftermath,
            unable to continue with her job, Rukia allows Ichigo to take on the role of a shinigami
            in her place as they together defeat the Hollows plaguing Ichigo's town.
        </synopsis>
        <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/3/20349.jpg</image>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>762</id>
        <title>Bleach: Memories in the Rain</title>
        <english>Bleach: Memories in the Rain</english>
        <synonyms>Bleach: Jump Festa 2004</synonyms>
        <episodes>1</episodes>
        <score>7.20</score>
        <type>Special</type>
        <status>Finished Airing</status>
        <start_date>2005-06-12</start_date>
        <end_date>2005-06-12</end_date>
        <synopsis>Kurosaki Ichigo, the temporary Shinigami(Death God) for Kuchiki Rukia, discovers
            his mother's killer as one of the Hollows he has been hunting. He does battle with it in
            a prideful battle of revenge. This Special is actually a flashback of previous episodes
            in Bleach. After the ending credits, a short plays showing Shinigami and their
            Zanpakutos to &amp;quot;Number One&amp;quot; from the Bleach Soundtrack. &lt;br /&gt;
        </synopsis>
        <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/5/21947.jpg</image>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>834</id>
        <title>Bleach: The Sealed Sword Frenzy</title>
        <english></english>
        <synonyms>Bleach: Jump Festa 2005</synonyms>
        <episodes>1</episodes>
        <score>7.05</score>
        <type>Special</type>
        <status>Finished Airing</status>
        <start_date>2006-03-23</start_date>
        <end_date>2006-03-23</end_date>
        <synopsis>A Shinigami named Baishin who was sealed by Soul Society long ago is set free on
            Earth. On a fateful day Ichigo encounters him and has roughly half of his reiatsu
            drained. Its now up to Ichigo and the Soul Society to finally put a stop to Baishin and
            his destruction.
        </synopsis>
        <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/1/834.jpg</image>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>1686</id>
        <title>Bleach: Memories of Nobody</title>
        <english>Bleach the Movie: Memories of Nobody</english>
        <synonyms>Bleach Movie I</synonyms>
        <episodes>1</episodes>
        <score>7.63</score>
        <type>Movie</type>
        <status>Finished Airing</status>
        <start_date>2006-12-16</start_date>
        <end_date>2006-12-16</end_date>
        <synopsis>In Karakura Town, there has been a sudden outbreak of unidentifiable spirits
            called &quot;blanks&quot; (vacant souls) while in the skies of Soul Society, the real
            world has been reflected. A mysterious female shinigami called Senna has appeared before
            Ichigo along with a man named Ganryu, leading a group called the &quot;Dark Ones.&quot;&lt;br
            /&gt;
            &lt;br /&gt;
            (Source: ANN)
        </synopsis>
        <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/1/1686.jpg</image>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>2889</id>
        <title>Bleach: The DiamondDust Rebellion</title>
        <english>Bleach the Movie 2: The DiamondDust Rebellion</english>
        <synonyms>Bleach Movie II; Bleach: The Diamond Dust Rebellion - Mou Hitotsu no Hyourinmaru
        </synonyms>
        <episodes>1</episodes>
        <score>7.65</score>
        <type>Movie</type>
        <status>Finished Airing</status>
        <start_date>2007-12-22</start_date>
        <end_date>2007-12-22</end_date>
        <synopsis>A valuable artifact known as &amp;quot;King's Seal&amp;quot; (&amp;quot;Ouin&amp;quot;)
            is stolen by a mysterious group of people during transport in the Soul Society. Toshiro
            Hitsugaya, the 10th Division Captain of Gotei 13, is assigned to transport the seal,
            fights the leader of the group, and shortly after, goes missing. After the incident, the
            Seireitei declares Hitsugaya a traitor and orders the capture and execution of
            Hitsugaya. Ichigo Kurosaki refuses to believe this, and along with Rangiku Matsumoto,
            Rukia Kuchiki, and Renji Abarai, swears to uncover the real mastermind of the stolen
            seal, find Hitsugaya, and clear his name. Meanwhile, a rogue Hitsugaya searches for the
            perpetrators and uncovers a dark secret regarding a long dead shinigami.&lt;br /&gt;
            &lt;br /&gt;
            (Source: ANN)
        </synopsis>
        <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/12/7499.jpg</image>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>4835</id>
        <title>Bleach: Fade to Black - Kimi no Na wo Yobu</title>
        <english>Bleach the Movie 3: Fade to Black</english>
        <synonyms>Bleach Movie III; Fade to Black: Call Out Your Name</synonyms>
        <episodes>1</episodes>
        <score>7.71</score>
        <type>Movie</type>
        <status>Finished Airing</status>
        <start_date>2008-12-13</start_date>
        <end_date>2008-12-13</end_date>
        <synopsis>A mysterious reiatsu (spiritual particle) explosion occurs in the center of
            Seireitei in Soul Society, causing it to be destroyed. At the exact same time, a major
            change overwhelms Kuchiki Rukia, which leaves her losing something important inside.
            Urahara Kisuke sends Kurosaki Ichigo to Soul Society to investigate the disturbance.
            Upon reaching Seireitei, Ichigo is set upon and attacked by shinigamis, once allies, who
            have no memory of him and Rukia. Now alone and on the run, Ichigo must find the missing
            Rukia and uncover the cause of the mysterious incident before it's too late. &lt;br /&gt;
            &lt;br /&gt;
            (Source: ANN)
        </synopsis>
        <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/3/64689.jpg</image>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <id>8247</id>
        <title>Bleach: Jigokuhen</title>
        <english>Bleach the Movie 4: Hell Verse</english>
        <synonyms>Gekijouban Bleach: Jigoku Hen; Bleach Movie IV; Bleach Movie 4; Bleach: The Hell
            Chapter
        </synonyms>
        <episodes>1</episodes>
        <score>7.80</score>
        <type>Movie</type>
        <status>Finished Airing</status>
        <start_date>2010-12-04</start_date>
        <end_date>2010-12-04</end_date>
        <synopsis>&amp;quot;Hell&amp;quot; is the place where a person is sent to who committed
            violent crimes when they were alive. Shinigami are forbidden to go there. One day,
            prisoners revolt and make their escape to Karakura&amp;mdash;the real world&amp;mdash;where
            Ichigo and his friends live in. Ichigo and his friends are defeated one after the other
            by prisoners with overwhelming power. A mysterious man appears who comes to their
            rescue. With Kokutou leading the way, Ichigo, Rukia, Uryuu, and Renji marche into Hell
            to save the world.&lt;br /&gt;
            &lt;br /&gt;
            Note: Episode 299 of Bleach serves as a prologue to this movie.&lt;br /&gt;
            &lt;br /&gt;
            (Source: AniDB, edited)
        </synopsis>
        <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/9/26792.jpg</image>
    </entry>
</anime>
